# Nanasaheb Yadav

Pune



nanayadav33@gmail.com



+91 9970673015



linkedin.com/in/nanasahebn



https://nanasaheb-yadav.github.io/Nanasaheb/

# Summary

5+ years of total experience, with 3.5 years of experience in Python Development.

Highly adept at Python Development, Python Automation, Data Migration, Web Automation and Scraping, REST API's, Testing and Deployment, Agile Methodologies.

Received Hall of Fame and Star Performer awards while working at Capgemini.

## **Experience**



## Associate- Projects

### Cognizant

Oct 2021 - Present (1 year +)

- Working as Data Engineer for data migration from Teradata to Snowflake.
- Responsible for automation using Python to migrate data from Teradata to Snowflake.
- Responsible for schema, data validation, bug resolutions, QA.
- Working on tools like Snowflake, Teradata, Postman, REST APIs, Git.
- Customization, use of REST APIs for automations using Python.

#### **Associate Consultant**

### Capgemini

Jan 2019 - Oct 2021 (2 years 10 months)

- Collaborated as integral part of team of 6 Python and 4 UIPath developers.
- Implemented 4+ software BOT's based on client needs using Python and UIPath.
- Worked on RPA, Web Automation, Web Scrapping using Python Selenium web driver, Data Analysis and Reporting.
- Developed 20+ use cases using Python, Selenium, UIPath and Databases (Oracle/MySQL) in 2 years.
- Adapted Agile software development process and DevOps.
- Compiled websites data for competitive analysis by performing web scrapping using Selenium, requests, Scrapy libraries and data analysis in python.
- Preprocess data and created reports using pandas, selenium, matplotlib, numpy, beautifulsoup libraries.



#### **Senior Analyst**

#### Capgemini

Dec 2017 - Dec 2018 (1 year 1 month)

- Experience building dashboards to show insights of different portfolios, dashboards, and detailed reports to higher management.
- Comfortable with accessing SQL databases and writing queries.
- Automated deployment process of 4000+ stores POS using Python and Power shell scripting.
- Performed functional and technical test execution activities as per test plan.
- Coordinated with development team to create test plans for enhancements and fixes on applications

- Remote POS Application and Packages deployment on 4000+ Starbucks stores.

# Analyst

Capgemini

Apr 2017 - Nov 2017 (8 months)

- Completed Java 8 training (JEE) in organization.
- Provided Level 2 support to Java projects.
- Hands-on Java/J2EE programming and diagnostic experience

### **Education**

Savitribai Phule Pune University

BE, Information Technology 2013 - 2016

SVERI's College of Engineering, Pandharpur

Diploma, Information Technology 2010 - 2013

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- **Web Application Technologies and Django** Coursera
- Introduction to Git and GitHub Coursera
- crash Course on Python Coursera
- Agile Software Development Coursera

#### Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Web Scraping • Agile Methodologies • REST APIs • Git • Data Migration • Snowflake • Selenium WebDriver • Selenium Testing • REST APIs

#### **Honors & Awards**

Star Performer Award - Capgemini
Jun 2021

Star Performer Award - Capgemini
Jun 2019

Hall of Fame Award - Capgemini Jun 2020